Fast and loud the strings ignite, running wild on Frisco
nights, history books with
missing lines, coyotes creeping back through time, never
thought they'd roam again, past
the branch and city bends, we drove 'em out in olden days,
but hunger finds its modern
way, steel and fog the Golden Gate, open pathways shifting
fate, through Marin they made their
claim, scratched the past it's not the same, lines are
drawn in yards and hearts, sidewalk
meetings, dog park barks, debate in every local bar, are we
safe for Orib war, out on
the streets again, coyotes running free, San Francisco
shaking out the old history, from
Marin they came, crossed the red steel frame, now the city
splits two sides of the coyote
game, how it the night, how it the night, back in the day
went the way 1895, we thought
they'd dead be gone but San Francisco survives, leaping
from the forest riding on the northbound
wind, sneak through the brazilio, a reckless oncoming, some
clutch their dogs tight, keep
the backyard light, kids off the grass, fear a yellow stare
at night, others see balance,
nature on patrol, clearing out the rats, chasing cats,
filling up the hole, out on the streets
again, coyotes running free, San Francisco shaking out the
old history, from Marin they
came, crossed the red steel frame, now the city splits two
sides of the coyote game,
how it the night, how it the night,